If the evangelical church would have acknowledged that racism and slavery was a sin, it couldn't have existed in Western culture.
There was a period of time that the white church was so powerful in its political stance and its influence in politics
that collectively, if the evangelical church in America would have stood together and said that this is a sin,
it never could have survived in the West the way it did.
How does that apply to the LGBTQIA plus community?
I think that it applies to all people that are human.
Humans should be treated with a level of grace and love the way that Jesus would want them to be treated.
Can you just say it one more time?
Every human being should be treated with a level of grace, mercy, and love the way that Jesus would want to treat them.
I do not believe in gay churches. I don't believe in white churches.
If you can't go to church, it's a problem with the church.
That individual church or with the community of church?
The ideology of what the church is from a Biblo-centric perspective.
Biblo-centric! Never heard that word!
I do not understand whether they do not want to pay attention to the church.
If you attempt it out, let's go to church.
You will BRANDON.
It's obviously bewildering, where they don't ought to retire.
Let's say you probably don't need to checkpoint it, but it's waiting for the church was to take the door and know what myel alma has to stand behind.
You never did not know what the church is having a needle in a之後 back to bids.